[{"answer": "Well, on and off, exactly what you're feeling right now.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Chad, in terms of just big picture, over the next eight hours here in New Orleans, I mean, until I think about 8:00 AM, you were saying before, what are we looking at, and for folks in this region?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "I absolutely do.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "Chad, are you still anticipating, though, about 20 inches of rain total here?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "The outer north part of the eyewall has made landfall now.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "but Chad, when are you anticipating landfall in Grand Isle?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "A handful.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "How many eyes have you been in in your lifetime?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well, it's pretty much the MO of this storm has been its big circulation.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "What's the significance of that?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Oh, yes (INAUDIBLE)", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "I don't know -- did you see that?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well, it's pouring in through the ceiling.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "So how much water do you think you have in your house now?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Even before the storm, you had a problem with salt water coming up the Mississippi, right?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "But how have you seen in the last hour in particular the atmosphere changing around you?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Yes, that's it.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Is that easy how to know that?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "And I suppose crucially, how do you think these reinforcements, which are multibillion reinforcements, are going to hold up to what is now going on?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Well, you know, every disaster is different and, you know, until people are testing with the kind of level of storm they had with Katrina, it's hard to compare.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "What do you feel?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Yes, that in (INAUDIBLE) absolutely is.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "And tell me Billy, is this the worst storm that you have seen in New Orleans since Katrina?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Do they feel confident in the local and state, and federal authorities that everything has been done that can could be done to protect them?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "What is going on?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "I would say that the levee is a lot better shape.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Are you confident that with all of the reinforcements, the billions and billions of dollars that was spent, are you confident we're not going to see any scenes even remotely like the appalling scenes that we saw in Katrina?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "What is the best advice that you would give them based on all of your experience from Katrina?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Go to the safest place in the home, gather everybody and you got to put some type of a mattress or something over you and your family and then call 911 and get a-hold of emergency services because the power line most likely will be down outside and it's in the dark.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "What do you do if your home is basically beginning to fall apart?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "You can see we really are in the midst of what is the most powerful rain band that we've had here all day.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Can you describe for me what is going on now?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "They are performing exactly as we anticipated they were.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "These are very expensive reinforced levees put in up to Katrina seven years to the day by extraordinary co-incidence, how do you believe they are holding up?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Absolutely, and we said that all along.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Is that the way you're reading it?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "We haven't heard any yet.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Are you getting any reports from local people yet of injuries or any extensive serious flooding?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Well, certainly the parishes in which they live all have emergency places where you can go and you can evacuate.", "docId": "120828pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "But if they start to suffer serious structural damage to their homes, what is the best thing to do then if they can't stay in their homes?", "qSentId": 523}]